我们来谈谈密码测试
Let's talk about the code tests.
根据公司的不同，密码测试是他们给你的东西。
The code tests is, depending on the
company, is something that they give you.
这可能是一个多小时的项目
It's probably gonna be
a multi hour project,
大概 5 到 10 个小时吧
maybe 5 to 10 hours, somewhere in there.
但他们想知道你是如何在更大的环境中编码的。
But they want to see how you
code in a larger environment.
密码测试是我个人在篱笆上的事
Code tests are something I
personally am on the fence about.
如果某人具有强大的 GitHub 或交付项目的历史，例如，
If someone has a robust GitHub or a
history of delivering projects, like yeah,
你在那个项目上工作好吗
you worked on that project, okay.
我可以查看他们的 GitHub ，我不能做代码测试。
I can check out their GitHub,
I may not do a code test.
但有很多公司你会得到一个代码测试。
But there are plenty of companies
you'll get a code test for.
这里有一些东西，肯定是你想做的一些小费。
Here are some of the things,
certainly some of the tips you want to do.
第一点，如果你忽略我说的其他内容，请注意。
Tip number one, if you ignore
everything else I say, follow this.
尽可能使您的代码可读。
Make your code as readable as possible.
别太聪明了
Don't try to be clever.
没人会用双字条代替 math.round 来表扬你
No one's gonna applaud you for
using double tilde instead of math.round.
是啊看起来很酷你就像是在看我是多么聪明
Yeah, it looks cool and you're like, wow,
look how they're gonna see how smart I am.
如果你读了很多代码评论你就不会想要聪明
If you're reading through many code
reviews, you're not gonna want cleverness,
您需要阅读代码。
you want readable code.
作为一名工程师如果我在读某人的代码评论
As an engineer,
if I'm reading someone's code review or
审查某人的密码测试我想看看他们是否知道密码
reviewing someone's code test I
want to see do they know the code.
这是一种代码，我想知道我是否加入了自己的代码库。
It's this type of code I want to see
if I come up in my code base itself.
这些都是我要检讨的政策。
These are the kind of
PRs I want to review.
就这样，别聪明了，只要把它弄明白就好了。
That's it, don't be clever,
just get it done and make it readable.
并对您的代码进行注释。
And comment your code.
直到我死的那天我会说你的代码
Until the day I die,
I'm gonna say comment your code.
有趣的是，不是每个人都同意我这样做。
Funny enough,
not everybody agrees with me on this.
有人说，代码应该是自记录的。
Some people say,
code should be self-documenting.
人们都这么说
People say that all the time.
酷，让它自我记录，但也要评论你的代码，就是它。
Cool, make it self-documenting, but
also comment your code, that's it.
特别是如果你读了很多密码测试
Especially if you're reading
a lot of code tests.
对您的代码进行注释，使其更易于理解。
Comment you code,
it makes it easier to understand.
好吧，我不同意他们做事的方式，但是
Okay, I don't necessarily agree with
the way they're doing things, but
我遵循他们的逻辑
I follow their logic.
因为他们告诉我他们在干什么
Because they told me
what they're doing and
我不需要花时间来解决这个问题。
I don't have to take
time to figure that out.
因为如果我得花时间弄明白我大概会喜欢
Because if I have to take time to
figure it out, I'll probably be like,
这太复杂了
this is too complicated, next.
这就是它的发展。
That's just how it goes.
你是个忙碌的人我是个忙碌的人
You're a busy person, I'm a busy person.
只需让您的代码可读，并对其进行注释并不要使其复杂化。
Just make your code readable, and
comment it and don't over complicate it.
试图像我说的那样很有诱惑力
It's tempting to try to be like I said,
clever.
简单的说，最好的代码是最简单的代码。
Just make it simple,
the best code is the simplest code.
最佳代码实际上是最小的代码量。
The best code is actually
the least amount of code.
如果有人打了什么就有 6 个不同的功能
If someone blows up something and
it's six different functions, and
不需要这么做会使它变得更加复杂
it doesn't need to be,
that's overcomplicating it.
保持干净，让它可读，不要让它太狂野。
Keep it clean, keep it readable,
don't make it too wild.
不要导入太多的库。
Don't import too many libraries.
图书馆不告诉我你知道什么
Libraries don't tell me what you know.
他们告诉我你知道如何去谷歌
They tell me that you know
how to Google things or
你知道怎么用别人知道的东西
you know how to use
what other people know.
这也是一种技能，但是
Which is a skill too, but
在这个特别的测试中我想知道你在干什么吗
in this particular test I'm trying to
see do you know what you're doing?
你知道怎么编码吗
Do you know how to code?
在这里导入一个库就可以了
It's okay to import a library here and
就在那里，这取决于那些给出密码测试的人是什么。
there, depending on what the people
who is giving the code test are.
有人说没有图书馆，有人说为所欲为。
Some people say no library,
some people say do whatever you want.
但即使他们说你可以使用 React 或 Angular ， Vue 或 Vue
But even if they say you can use React or
Angular or Vue or
不管你想要什么我都不会去进口图书馆
whatever you want, I wouldn't go
overboard on importing libraries.
最好尽量把它保持简单
It's better to keep it
as simple as possible.
我一般都坚持 " 洛达什 " ，只是实用功能。
I generally stick to Lodash,
just utility functions.
我可以编这些实用程序但很不错是有人为我做的
I could code up these utility functions,
but it's nice that someone did it for me.
但他们不会作弊的
But they're not cheating anyway.
如果您在末尾有任何时间作为顶部的樱桃，请添加某些单元测试。
If you have any time at the end,
as a cherry on top, add some unit tests.
这个人是一个圆形的工程师。
This person is a well rounded engineer.
他们不只是想把工作做了
They don't just think about
getting the job done,
他们会想到可维护性
they think about maintainability.
他们会思考这个代码是如何在一段时间里生存的。
They think about how this
code is gonna live over time.
如果您对代码测试有任何疑问，请询问问题。
And if you have any questions
on the code test, ask questions.
我知道，如果你有问题，问问题，但你经常不问。
I know, if you have questions,
ask questions, but you often don't.
可以免费向该人员发送邮件并进行说明。
Feel free to email that person back and
say.
哎，我有个问题，我不太了解要求，
Hey, I have a question on, I don't
really understand the requirements,
或者这对我来说是不清楚的问问题
or this is unclear to me, ask questions.
你最好提前问问题你别傻了
It's better to ask questions ahead
of time, you won't look silly.
不做密码测试也是完全错误的
Than to do the code test and
it's completely wrong.
他们就像这样我们最好让你重做
And they're like, well,
at best we're gonna ask you to redo it.
在最坏的情况下他们会后悔的，不，下一个
At worst they're gonna be like sorry,
no, next.
你浪费了你的时间浪费了他们的时间
And you wasted your time,
you wasted their time.
所以请提前提问。
So ask questions ahead of time.